"Namu Amida Butsu"
"Namu Amida Butsu" Believe it or not,
the world is filled with strange phenomena
"Namu Amida Butsu"
that science is yet to explain.
That science is yet to explain.
And when people come face to face with them,
they are helplessly thrown
into the dark depths of fear.
But there are those who fight every day
to shine a ray of hope
into that chaotic darkness.
People call them...
"Psychics"
" psychics. "
There's no doubt about it...
What I saw was not of this world.
I knew there was something
wrong with this property
since I bought it dirt cheap.
I've never been the type to
worry about stuff like that.
But fields are at their most vulnerable
in the days leading up to a harvest.
So I got worried one night,
went to check on things,
and that's when I saw it.
Something was wriggling back and forth,
dancing on my fields!
The next morning, I found
all of my crops withered away.
I only started farming to kill time,
but this has been going on for three years.
"Amino Acid Fertilizer Potting Compost" I only started farming
to kill time, but this has been going on for three years.
"Amino Acid Fertilizer
Potting Compost"
"Amino Acid Fertilizer Potting
Compost" It's starting to creep me out now.
It's starting to creep me out now.
My next harvest is coming up,
so that's why I gave you a call.
I figured I needed the help of
someone with psychic powers.
A wise decision, sir.
But, you see...
Next year, my idiot son will be
starting high school, so...
As for your fees...
You don't think you can pay?
It would depend on how much, but...
Well, I am running a business here,
so I'm going to need
some form of compensation.
"Executing the Exorcism!!" "Option A -- Trial Course" "A Mere 2,000 yen" "Option B -- Serious Course" "A Mere
5,000 yen" "Option C -- All-Out Course" "A Mere 12,000 yen" so I'm going to need some form of compensation.
So I'm going to need
some form of compensation.
"Refer us to a friend now and get an extra 5%
reduction!! Also get an add-on exorcism for 20% off!!"
"Refer us to a friend now and get an extra 5% reduction!!
Also get an add-on exorcism for 20% off!!" Right...
Right...
Let's see. If I'm able to exorcise
whatever it is that's haunting your fields...
...I'll take 30% of your upcoming harvest!
He's okay with veggies as payment?
I looked into this a bit on my own,
but I don't see any issues
with the fertilizer or the soil.
Meaning there's not much
I can do about this situation.
What do you think, Mob?
Again, could you not summon me
on such short notice?
This could be the work of
those daikon fairies.
Do those even exist?
Did you see something move just now?
Actually...
It's rather weak,
but I do sense an aura.
I heard you yappin' earlier today, too.
You gonna exorcise me?
Mob, let's take care of this quickly.
Okay.
Is that it?
Yes. It was just possessing the scarecrow,
so it probably couldn't do much harm.
What the heck is that?
Oh, that would be the spirit's true form.
So the scarecrow was a decoy?!
"High-Level Spirit"
"Wriggle Wriggle"
" High-Level Spirit" "VVriggle VVriggle" This
is my land, and I won't let anyone else have it!
"High-Level Spirit"
"Wriggle Wriggle"
Then show me the deed!
Do you have any idea how hard it is
to grow crops until harvest?
Talk about a twisted way to harass someone!
It's not like I'm letting
the crops go to waste.
Did you actually think
that spirits can't eat?
You guys don't need nutrients!
I can absorb the life force of all the crops
that grow in these fields.
So don't worry. They're serving
their purpose as my food.
You wretched vegetable thief...
Mob! Blast him!
Okay.
Not bad, kid.
But it appears your friend here
is as ordinary as they come.
Master!
I'll turn you both into fertilizer!
It's no use! What you're destroying is
but a tiny portion of the plants I control.
But keep it up, and I'll instantly kill
your friend and rip him to pieces!
You're indeed a child.
How naive. You should've known
you were both going to die anyway.
Since destroying the vines
doesn't hurt the spirit itself...
...it must not be possessing them.
It's controlling living things
like a remote control car.
I've never even thought about doing that.
I wonder if I can do it, too...
The same thing as an evil spirit.
You brat!
The plants stopped moving?
I tried ordering the plants.
When I sent them a stronger signal
than the evil spirit,
I was able to control them.
That's the correct solution.
I'm glad you were able to realize it.
C-Curse you, you brat!
How dare you overwrite
my command over these plants?!
Damn it... You'll pay for this!
Die!
What?!
Huh?
What is that?
I thought I'd start a home garden.
If it works out, we can save money on food.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" The veggies
we were supposed to get as payment were a bust,
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
but he gave me some soil, fertilizer,
and vegetable seeds instead.
"3 times a day! Organic Fertilizer" "Liquid Fertilizer" "Humus"
but he gave me some soil, fertilizer, and vegetable seeds instead.
"3 times a day! Organic Fertilizer"
"Liquid Fertilizer" "Humus"
Oh, and here. Your pay for that last job.
Broccoli seeds.
I'm getting paid in kind now...
Thank you very much.
Oh, right.
I planted some cherry tomatoes in here.
Why don't you put some energy into it
and see if you can make them grow?
Okay.
Whoa, that's amazing!
I smell a new business opportunity!
"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee on 1 of them
will be on the house!!" I smell a new business opportunity!
"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism
fee on 1 of them will be on the house!!"
"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee
on 1 of them will be on the house!!" Let's see...
"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism
fee on 1 of them will be on the house!!"
"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee on 1
of them will be on the house!!" It tastes like crap.
It tastes like crap.
"Umami 0%"
"Umami 0%" You can take these
cherry tomatoes home with you.
"Umami 0%"
" Umami 0%"
Huh?
"Umami 0%"
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
Can't you feel your own frustration?
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
What do you want to be?
Wear your overflowing emotions
on your sleeve and break it down
What do you see once you go
beyond your limits?
(99.9! 99.9!)
The mysterious percentage
Cr yin' my life, or yin' my psyche,
Cr yin' my heart in such commonplaces!
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind?
It all begins when it hits 100
The MOB is alive. The MOB is high.
The MOB is staying frustrated, aren't you?
Is that your ideal?
Is that your mind? Right now
YOUR LIFE IS YOUR OWN.
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
"Mob Psycho 100 I|"
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Welcome, my fellow upper echelon members
of the Psycho Helmet Religion.
"We're Looking For Our God. The Psycho Helmet Religion" Welcome,
my fellow upper echelon members of the Psycho Helmet Religion.
Welcome, my fellow upper echelon members
of the Psycho Helmet Religion.
Let us begin our 12th official meeting.
As for today's agenda,
we'll be discussing the head temple
for our Psycho Helmet Religion.
Actually, before we get into that,
I have a question.
Has there been any progress in
the search for our beloved founder?
He has not been found yet.
Many men have claimed to be the founder,
but they were all impostors.
At the (LOL) gathering,
I saw his face up close,
so I'm the one verifying these claims.
I can guarantee they are false.
But I promise to bring our founder
before you very soon.
Yeah, right. I know the kid to begin with.
I'm going to keep riling up these believers
and make Mob-kun a cult star.
But the biggest obstacle here
is Mob-kun himself.
"Arithmetic I" But the biggest
obstacle here is Mob-kun himself.
"Arithmetic I"
"Arithmetic I" Right now, there's
no way he could lead anyone.
Right now, there's no way
he could lead anyone.
I need him to grow more as a person.
There has to be a way...
Something that'll make Mob-kun grow.
I...
...Kamuro Shinji,
hereby resign from my position
as student council president as of today.
What?
I spread false rumors about fellow students
and accused them of crimes they didn't
commit, and that's why I'm resigning.
Therefore, an election for the next student
council president will be held very soon.
That's it! This is perfect!
Something to help Mob-kun grow!
But there's no reason
Mob-kun would want to run.
How do I...
I wonder who the next
president is going to be.
Right?
I just hope they're a good person,
if nothing else.
Ah, it's Tsubomi-chan.
She's as cute as ever.
You're staring way too hard again.
--Mezato-san?!
--And you're panicking too much.
So you do like Takane-san.
Wha... How did you...
What's with that reaction?
I never expected you to
fall for the school's idol.
I guess even you can be
rather superficial, too.
I honestly don't get
what you see in her, though.
I've been friends with Tsubomi-chan
since we were little.
Oh, she's the school's idol?
I see...
How did two childhood friends end up
in such drastically different situations?
Under normal circumstances,
you'd have no chance with her,
but right now, you have a
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity!
What do you mean?
"Student Council"
"Student Council" The seat of
student council president is vacant!
The seat of student council
president is vacant!
Right now, Takane-san is
way out of your league,
but what if you were
student council president?
"Student Council President"
You'd go shooting up the ranks!
You might be able to close the gap
between you and your school idol!
I wouldn't mind helping you out
if you're thinking about running.
You'll owe me one, though.
This is the perfect opportunity to show
people who you really are, Mob-kun!
"Hardcore Training Montage"
"Hardcore Training Montage" And on
that day, Mob's hardcore training began.
"Hardcore Training Montage"
Finally, a week later...
"Student Council President Candidate Speech
Competition" Finally, a week later...
"Student Council President Candidate
Speech Competition"
"Student Council President Candidate Speech Competition" We will
now begin the election to decide our next student council president.
"Student Council President Candidate
Speech Competition"
"Student Council President Candidate Speech
Competition" There are a total of four candidates.
There are a total of four candidates.
Our first candidate is
Morishige Kyohei-kun from Class 2-2.
Each candidate gave their speech.
Next, from Class 3-4,
we have Kamuro Shinji-kun.
Wait,
Didn't he resign?
President, why did you resign
without discussing it with us?
I'm just as responsible for what we did!
Resigning is no way to take responsibility.
You're still running away,
which achieves nothing.
Stand for election again,
and if you do get elected...
Yeah. That'll be my opportunity
to truly make things right.
And finally, Mob's turn arrived.
Nii-san?
What the heck is he doing?
Wait, Mob-kun?
You practiced your speech over and over--
not to mention I basically wrote it for you.
You've got this!
Kageyama! It's all about guts!
You pulled a fast one on me, White T Poison.
You're not content with ruling
the school from the shadows?
I was planning on supporting
President Kamuro,
but this changes everything.
Kageyama Shigeo-kun from Class 2-1.
Please begin.
And it's over.
Each candidate is given five minutes
for their campaign speech,
and he was the first person ever
to not say a single word in that time.
"Student Council President Election Voting Results" "1st
Kamuro" "2nd Nakayama" " 3rd Morishige" " 4th Kageyama "
He won't cut it as the founder like this.
I need him to be better.
I never should've done that.
This one did a number on him.
He's not moving at all.
Go on home for the day, okay?
"Telepathy Club" "Body Improvement
Club" Go on home for the day, okay?
"Telepathy Club"
"Body Improvement Club"
"Telepathy Club" "Body Improvement
Club" Yes, sir. I'm very sorry.
"I'll be waiting for you behind the school."
W-Wait, this is...
When I saw you muster the courage to take
the podium despite being so uncomfortable,
I ended up falling for you, Kageyama-kun.
Um...
Please go out with me.
"Progress Toward
Mob's Explosion"
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 21%"
"Mob Psycho 100 I|"
"Telepathy Club"
"Body Improvement Club"
"Telepathy Club" "Body
Improvement Club" Kageyama-kun.
Kageyama-kun.
Let's walk home together.
Oh, but I have club...
Go on, Kageyama.
Today's menu is free training, anyway.
Thank you, Captain Musashi.
Huh?
Mob-kun has a girlfriend?
What's going on? Is this some
supernatural phenomenon?
What the heck's happening?
But man, I'm so envious...
So what do you usually do, Kageyama-kun?
Um...
I do some running with
the Body Improvement Club.
Other than that, I help
an acquaintance with their work.
--What kind of work?
--Huh? Oh, ghost--
L-It's sort of like a bookstore.
What? You work part-time at
a bookstore, Kageyama-kun?
That's amazing!
N-No, it's not a big deal...
I only help out with really simple things.
Still, it is amazing!
I'd love to work at a bookstore.
I'm already lying to her.
But I think telling her I have
an exorcism job will creep her out.
You look a little pale. Are you okay?
Yeah. Hey, you like books, Emi-san?
Well... I do like books, but...
I guess I don't mind telling you, Kageyama-kun.
I'm writing a novel.
Huh? Wow, that's amazing!
What's amazing about that?
Oh, you don't care, huh?
Sorry.
No, I really think it's amazing!
I'm just bad with words.
Maybe I'll have you read it sometime.
I haven't shown anyone else,
so it'd be pretty embarrassing for me.
But this counts as practice, too.
Sure, I'll read it.
And every day after that,
Mob walked home from school with Emi.
Hey, Mob. You're home early again.
Did you quit your club?
No, I'm actually heading back to school now.
Huh?
Why the heck did he
bother coming home, then?
Hey, Mob. You seem more
cheerful than usual today.
You exorcism game is on point, too.
You think so? I can't really tell myself.
Did you get a girlfriend?
As if!
I'm done with the exorcism,
so I'm going home now.
"Bye.
"Huh?
"What?"
What?
Seconds, please.
Wow, this is rare.
Our Shige asking for seconds.
What's up, Shigeo? Did you use
too much of your psychic powers?
No, it's not like that.
I thought Nii-san would be
bummed out about the election,
but I'm glad to see he's more than fine.
"One Week Later"
Are you done reading?
What do you think?
It's really good... I think.
You know a lot of big words.
If you don't get it, just say so.
Sorry! That's not what I meant!
I really did pay attention to every word!
Say, Kageyama-kun...
It's been a week since I asked you out.
You rejected me then,
so why do you still walk home with me?
Is it because you felt bad for me?
Huh? No, it's nothing like that.
I also know you were going back
to your club after you got home.
You keep trying not to hurt my feelings.
Are you sure it's not pity?
I feel sort of pathetic.
I-I'm sorry. That's not my intention.
And all you do is apologize.
I don't understand how you feel at all.
Or could it be...
...that you don't even have feelings?
--Huh?
--Like, your own opinions.
You froze up in your campaign speech, too.
Did you only run for president
because someone told you to?
Well...
The truth is, I'm sort of like that, too.
You are?
The reason I asked you out
was because of a dare.
We thought your silent speech was hilarious,
so my friends and I played
rock-paper-scissors, and I lost.
I was afraid I'd be a laughingstock
if you turned me down,
but since you started walking home with me,
they never found out you actually did.
Thanks.
But I figured it was about time I told you.
Sorry for lying to you for the past week.
A novel? Seriously? You're too funny!
Let me read it!
Damn, you wrote a lot! What the hell?
Hey, come on. Don't just read it like that.
It's really embarrassing.
Are you actually writing
this seriously, Emi?
Of course not. I was just a little bored.
How bored could you possibly be
to write this crap?
Instead of wasting your time writing
this drivel, go to the arcade with us!
It's not like I spend all my time on it.
Hey, stop that. You're littering.
No, if you're going to do it,
make sure it's all ripped up.
Stop... that.
--Who are you?
--Kageyama-kun?
Oh, hey! It's that guy!
The one who turned into
a statue during his speech!
Wow, so he can talk.
What the hell's your problem?
Still think you're dating Emi?
She only asked you out on a dare, dude.
Hilarious.
She's not your girlfriend!
It's really mean of you to rip up
the novel she worked so hard to write.
Huh?
You said it was just to kill time, right?
Y-Yeah. Something like that.
What the hell's your problem? Get a clue.
Scram.
Didn't you hear me? Get outta here!
I don't think this is trash.
If you're going to throw
it away, I'LL take it.
I made the decision to
consider my feelings more.
And you need to pick up
things you feel are important.
Wh-What the hell is he talking about?
Talk about creepy...
Emi?!
You guys can head home.
Oh, really?
Okay, then.
Bye-bye.
Aw...
What are we even doing?
Wanna chase after them?
But... Thank you.
"No going back..."
Forget this. I can just write it again.
You see...
"Adventure"
...I happen to be an esper.
...| happen to be an esper.
Thank you, Kageyama-kun.
Smooth.
Everyone is dreaming "Ripped
Apart - Someone ls Watching~"
"Ripped Apart
- Someone ls Watching~"
Of a world filled with bright futures
"Ripped Apart - Someone ls Watching~"
What? Seriously?
Of a world filled with bright futures
Of a world filled with bright futures If something
that fun was going on, you should've called me!
If something that fun was going on,
you should've called me!
I'm sure that it's painted in vivid colors If something
that fun was going on, you should've called me!
I'm sure that it's painted in vivid colors
I'm sure that it's painted in vivid colors I never would've
expected you to show someone your powers on your own!
I never would've expected you to show
someone your powers on your own!
That have nothing to do with me I never would've
expected you to show someone your powers on your own!
That have nothing to do with me
So, what happened after that'?
What do you mean'?
That have nothing to do with me
With that Emi girl or whatever.
"Why am I crying?"
"Why am I crying?" Did her attitude toward
you change when she saw your powers?
Did her attitude toward you change
when she saw your powers?
"Should I be hated by someone?"
"Should I be hated by someone?" Did she go, "I've
really fallen for you now," or something like that?
"Should I be hated by someone?"
"Should I be hated by someone?" That would
never happen just because I have psychic powers.
That would never happen just
because I have psychic powers.
"When did this all happen?" That would never
happen just because I have psychic powers.
"When did this all happen?"
Really? Is that how it is?
The answers are nowhere to be found
Psychic powers, huh...
My emotions began to stir and
whispered faintly in a blue tone
My emotions began to stir and whispered faintly
in a blue tone Kageyama-kun sure is amazing.
My emotions began to stir and
whispered faintly in a blue tone
My emotions began to stir and whispered faintly in a blue
tone A middle school student... with psychic powers...
A middle school student...
with psychic powers...
I still remember all the words that came flooding
out A middle school student... with psychic powers...
I still remember all the words
that came flooding out
I still remember all the words that came flooding out
More importantly, you tell tor another love letter'?
More importantly, you fell
for another love letter?
I don't know when it happened, but my heart has started
opening up More importantly, you fell for another love letter?
I don't know when it happened,
but my heart has started opening up
I don't know when it happened, but my heart has started opening
up Looks like you'll always need an advisor like me, Shigeo!
I don't know when it happened,
but my heart has started opening up
From now on, I'll always stay by your side!
That's gross.
You're not nice to me, but I knew that.
"Progress Toward
Mob's Explosion"
"Japanese Dictionary" "Delicious Vegetables" "Progress Toward Mob's
Explosion: 27%" "Lifting Weights ls the Best Answer to Everything"
Let's go to Cuticle City
in search of urban legends!
Human-Faced Dog, Dash Granny,
Red Raincoat, the Dragger, and many more!
I'm leaving the rest to you, Mob!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ll Episode 2:
"Urban Legends
- Encountering Rumors~."
- Encountering Rumors~"
" Urban Legends - En<counterring Rumors~ "
VVatching ll in real time is also a wise decision.
"Urban Legends
- Encountering Rumors~"